# CÉSAR GARCÍA CABEZA

### **Software Engineer graduate**

- **J** +34 648035992
- Pola de Siero, Spain
- themrcesi.github.io

### **EDUCATION**

## M.Sc. in Artificial Intelligence

### **Technical University of Madrid**

- **September 2020 July 2021**
- Madrid, Spain
- Average grade: 9.14 (out of 10).

### B.Sc. in Computer Science

### Wroclaw University of Science & Technology

**2018 - 2019** 

- Wroclaw, Poland
- Erasmus exchange during the academic course 2018/2019.

# B.Eng. in Computer Software Engineering

### **University of Oviedo**

**2016 - 2020** 

- Oviedo, Spain
- Coursed 204 ECTS in English.
- Average grade: 8.33 (out of 10).

## **EXPERIENCE**

### Software Engineer Collaborator

### StockFink

February 2021 - Present

### Software Engineer Intern

### **DAIL Software**

April 2021 - June 2021

#### Research Intern

### **Biomedical Informatics Group, Technical University of Madrid**

September 2020 - September 2020

### Undergraduate Research Intern

### **UNIMODE** Research Group, University of Oviedo

September 2019 – October 2019

Oviedo, Spain

The following tasks were performed in collaboration with two professors of the Computation and Artificial Intelligence department:

- Analysis and optimization of algorithms.
- Development of algorithms.

The previous tasks were applied to a specific problem: aggregation of partially ordered sets. This work set a baseline for my Final Degree Project, obtaining later a grade of 10.

# LIFE PHILOSOPHY

" Always ready to learn new things. If I have a goal, I don´t stop until I get it."

### **ABOUT ME**

Software engineer graduate with a passion for data, technology & artificial intelligence especially machine and deep learning and its real-life applications such as natural language processing.

I am a passionate lover of sports, having played: football, basketball, volleyball, tennis, panel, fronton, badminton, snowboard... But, without any doubt, Judo is, and will always be, my real passion. Judo has been present in my life since I was 6 years old, and nowadays I have the black belt, 2° DAN. Thanks to this incredible sport I have learnt essential values such as respect, self control, perseverance and overcoming.

# **STRENGTHS**

Motivator & Leader Curious

Hard-working Problem solving

Ability to work in team

# **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Software Design & Development **Computer Vision** Pvthon Information Retrieval NLP Machine and Deep Learning Web Scrapping Agile Methods Scikit-learn Docker Keras Tensorflow PyTorch Dask Git React Numpy **Pandas** 

# **SCHOLARSHIPS**

### **Erasmus+ Grant**

### **University of Oviedo**

**September 2018 - June 2019** 

Oviedo, Spain

### **Excellent Academic Achievement Scholarship**

### **University of Oviedo**

**September 2016 - June 2017** 

Oviedo, Spain

# **CERTIFICATIONS**

# Python for Data Science and Machine Learning Bootcamp **Udemy**

**i** July 2021

Skills: Numpy, Pandas, Seaborn, Matplotlib, PLotly, Scikit-Learn, Machine Learning.

### **Deep Learning Specialization**

#### Coursera

January 2021

Skills: Neural Networks, Convolutional Neural Networks, Recurrent Neural Networks, Keras, Tensorflow.

# Machine Learning, Data Science and Deep Learning with Python Udemy

August 2020

Skills: Python, Numpy, Pandas, Scikit-learn, Machine Learning, Recommender Systems, Neural Networks.

# **COURSES**

### First-Aid

### Cruz Roja

March 2014 - May 2014

# **VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE**

### Volunteer

### **Erasmus Student Network Oviedo**

**September 2019 - Present** 

### **LANGUAGES**

Spanish English French



C1 Advanced

### **Cambridge Assesment English**

**=** 2017

Delf B1

### Alliance Française

**2015**